studyco.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy

StudyCo Pty Ltd is committed to protecting your online privacy by abiding by privacy laws.

####  **Personal Information**

  * It is our usual practice to collect personal information directly from you.
  * Sometimes we collect personal information from a third party if you have consented or would reasonably expect us to collect the information in this way, for example from publicly available sources such as websites or telephone directories.
  * We do not collect personal information about you if you only browse this website. This website only uses session cookies during the login and shopping process.

####  **Uses**

  * We only use your personal information for the purposes for which you give it to us and for related, internal management purposes.
  * We do not give information about you to government agencies, organisations or anyone else unless one of the following applies:
    * you have consented
    * you'd expect us to or we have told you we will
    * it is required or authorised by law
    * it will prevent or lessen a serious & imminent threat to somebody's life or health or
    * the disclosure is reasonably necessary for law enforcement or for the protection of public revenue.
  * We analyse non-identifiable website traffic data to improve our services.  

###  **Your Choices**

  * You may access personal information that we hold about you or you can ask us to correct personal information we hold about you.
  * If you are on one or more of our email lists you may opt out of further contact from us by clicking the unsubscribe option in all emails.

###  **Important Information**

  * StudyCo Pty Ltd is bound by the Information Privacy Principles of the Privacy Act 1988.
  * Our website follows the Privacy Commissioner's Guidelines for Federal and ACT Government Websites.

###  **Security Capabilities & Policy **

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

When you place an order through this website, we need to know your name, e-mail, phone number, address.

**What about Cookies?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. They allow you to place your online order and to login once you are subscribed. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. You will need cookies enabled to use StudyCo Pty Ltd [website](http://www.studyco.com/).

**Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by StudyCo Pty Ltd. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

###  **Refund Policy - Fraud Policy**

**Refund Policy**

As part of our commitment the fee charged for our university application services is non-refundable. Under compelling circumestances and in case no services are not given to the student becasue an unavailibility of StudyCo Pty Ltd, the application fee is refunded back to the student. For obtaining more information of service fees please click [here](http://www.studyco.com/Article/11269-Free_of_Charge_Services).

Please retain your Invoice/receipt of [university application fee](http://www.studyco.com/Article/11269-Free_of_Charge_Services), as we require proof of purchase before any refunds can be processed. If you need to change your program of study you are required to pay the extra application fee relevent to the course of study.

We aim to provide you with quality services to satisfy your needs. If you are dissatisfied with or have any complaints about any of our  services, please email us at [inquiries@studyco.com](mailto:enquiries@genovese.com.au). We will answer your emails as quickly as possible. This is our promise to you because your satisfaction is our primary concern. We advise all our customers to review this privacy policy and refund policy page frequently as this Policy may be amended by us at any time without specific notice to you. The latest Policy will be posted on this site and you should review this Policy prior to using this site.

###  **Fraud Policy Statement**

**StudyCo Pty Ltd** considers the act of fraud as a very serious matter and as such the website is committed to set out a strategy that is designed to frustrate any attempted act of fraudulent or corruption within the transactions made for colleges/schools programs. StudyCo Pty Ltd introduces appropriate measures to minimise the risk of fraud and adopts formal procedures to investigate fraud when it is suspected.

In order to maintain StudyCo Pty Ltd high standards, procedures and controls have been established to provide an environment which will minimise the opportunity for fraud. These procedures and controls help us conduct our business in a manner beyond reproach. Our commitment regarding online security is simple. If assets are taken from your account in an unauthorized online transaction on studyco.com and you've followed the steps described in the **Your responsibilities** section below—we will reimburse the assets taken from your account in the unauthorized transaction. 

###  **Your responsibilities**

**Review your accounts regularly**

  * Check your account frequently. Promptly and completely review all information we send you.

  * Report any errors or discrepancies in your account and any suspected unauthorized transactions or account changes to Vanguard immediately.

**Protect your studyco.com user name, password, and other account-related information**

  * Make sure your user name, password, & answers to security questions are unique and strong.

  * Never share your user name, password, or other account-related information with anyone.

  * Never store your user name, password, or answers to security questions in your browser.

  * Clear any temporarily stored copies of online information by closing your browser after signing off. Do not leave your computer unattended while logged on to Vanguard.com.

**Protect your computer**

Make certain that any computer you use to access Vanguard.com has up-to-date security and anti-spyware, antivirus, and firewall software.

**Do not reply to e-mail requests for personal or financial information**

Do not respond to, open an attachment in, or click on a link within an e-mail if you suspect the message is fraudulent. Vanguard will not ask for personal information such as your Social Security number, account numbers, or passwords in an e-mail.

**Cooperate  with us and stay informed**

Cooperate fully with StudyCo Pty Ltd in investigating and prosecuting any unauthorized activity in your account, and follow our recommendations about how to protect your account. We may require you to file a police report, complete a notarized affidavit, or permit access to your computer.

**How to contact us**

Corporate Governance | StudyCo Pty Ltd

PO Box 180, Collins Street West,

Melbourne, Victoria, 8007, Australia 

T: +61 3 9629 2677

F: +61 3 9629 2611

W: www.studyco.com
